Srinivasan Chakkarapani

Digital Product Designer (UI-UX)

www.srinivasan.design +1 312-973-6557 tcsreeni93@gmail.com

Summary

I'm a product designer creating digital products with delightful experiences. Solving problems via digital products has been my passion over the years with a penchant designing interfaces for new age devices like smartphones and wearables. I have a strong belief that a good product is a concoction of design, experience and technology.

Education

MS Human Computer Interaction

DePaul University, 2020 (Expected)

Bachelors in Computer Science & Engineering

SASTRA University, 2015

Professional Experience

Interaction Designer, Zeta

February 2018 - August 2018

Worked as as an interaction designer for various multiple stealth mode web products bundled inside the Zeta Optima product which focuses on digitising the tax benefits of employees. Intiated & framed a design system for products across web and mobile platforms.

Product Designer, Zoho Corporation

December 2015 - January 2018

Designed and shipped the Zoho Sheet product as the primary product designer. As the only designer, I worked on the application's mobile platforms (i.e.) iOS, Android from ideating features, wireframing to setting visual standards and framing a design platform. Worked Closely with the developers, Product managers to effectively ship the product to the respective stores.

Product Designer, Holachef

June 2015 - December 2015

Designed the iOS and Android Application for the company. Also wore the hat of web designer in designing the primary web product. Also helped in designing various back end applications that helped in the working of the product cycle.

Key Skills

Information Architecture

User Research

Wireframing

Interaction Design

Visual Design

Prototyping

Motion Design

Usablity Testing

Design Systems

Mobile Design

Web Design

User Interviews

Low/ High fidelity mockups

Tools

Wireframing

Balsamiq, Axure RP

Design

Sketch, Adobe Photoshop & Illustrator, Figma.

Prototyping

Principle, Adobe After Effects, Framer X, Marvel, Invision.

Development

Sublime Text, Adobe Dreamweaver.

Languages

HTML, CSS, Javascript